#### **PROFILE**

Recent I.T. graduate with 13 years of working in a wide variety of teams and leading some along the way. Ability to selfmanage, support others, and contribute to building a successful team. Experience in communicating with others of various positions from coworkers to managers via over the phone or in person. Personal experience with building PC's as a hobby and ready to build professional experience in I.T. Have worked in different types of jobs requiring troubleshooting and technical issue resolving as problems arose. Received entry-level certifications in general computer technician, security, networking, and have worked with different types of operating systems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Title Associate**

CRB Auto | 2500 Paseo Verde Pkwy Suite 100 Henderson, NV 89074 | July 2019 - Current

- Title release according to State and corporate guidelines for paid-in-full accounts.
- Interact with customers, internal departments, state motor vehicle departments, and dealerships regarding titles.
- Track and follow up on titles for various reasons.

## **Customer Service Associate**

CRB Auto | 2500 Paseo Verde Pkwy Suite 100 Henderson, NV 89074 | Nov 2017- July 2019

- Assist customers with payments over the phone, status of car loan, and loan questions.
- Provided password resets and general website/mobile app support to customers.
- Update, review and follow up with account information as appropriate.

# **Call Center Agent/Supervisor**

Alorica | 6320 S Pecos Rd #123 Las Vegas, NV 89120 | Oct 2016 - Nov 2017

- Assist members with benefits, provider searches, PCP changes, and any other questions.
- Assist providers with claims, member benefits, and directing calls to other departments.
- Assist a team of 10 agents, deescalate calls, and provide coaching for agents in deescalating calls.

## Salesclerk/Computer Department

Curacao Retail Store | 4300 Meadows Ln Las Vegas, NV 89107 | Sep 2016-Oct 2016

- Advised customers on products, provided information on warranties, and finalized sales.
- Created credit accounts for customers and took payments for credit accounts.
- Organized and took inventory of products on hand and in storeroom.

## **Customer Book Finder/Clerk**

eFollett | 3200 E Cheyenne Ave North Las Vegas, NV 89030 | Aug 2016 - Sep 2016

- Assisted students with textbooks, supplies, and prepared online orders for pickup.
- Checked out students, signed up for book rental services, and handled V.A. Grant purchases.
- Maintained stock and cleanliness of store.

# **Quality Control Technician/Supervisor**

Poly-West Inc | 251 Conestoga Way Henderson, NV 89002 | Sep 2010 - Aug 2016

- Tested plastic products made on site to make sure it met standards and kept log of results.
- Released product that was up to standards and held products not up to standard.
- Oversaw a team of 8 Q.C. technician's on breaks, productivity, and test being performed.
- Made decision on final displacement of product and dealt with complaints/concerns.
- Coordinated with management to maintain workflow and productivity on floor/lab.
- Entered daily results in to a AS400 system & reported findings to upper management.

#### Clerk

CVS Pharmacy | 2594 Wigwam Pkwy Henderson, NV 89074 | Nov 2007 - Oct 2010

- Assisted customers with finding what they made need & stocked the store.
- Reorganized back room and cooler to a more efficient manner.
- Received orders from venders and made sure that order was correct.

# Angel Ocampo



702-789-8791



Ocampoangel89@gmail.com



4937 Ronan Dr Las Vegas, NV 89110

# Education

# **High School Diploma**

Rancho High School | 2004 - 2008 1900 E Searles Ave Las Vegas, NV 89101

#### **Associate of Science General Studies**

College of Southern Nevada | 2008-2015 3200 E Cheyenne Ave N Las Vegas, NV 89030

# **Bachelor of Science Information Technology**

Western Governors University | 2016 -2020 4001 S Edmond St, Las Vegas, NV 89118

# Certifications

MTA: Networking Fundamentals - Certified 2017 CompTIA A+ Certification - Certified 2018 CompTIA Security+ Certification - Certified 2018 CompTIA Network+ Certification - Certified 2019 CompTIA Project+ Certification - Certified 2020 CompTIA Cloud Essentials - Certified 2020 CIW Site Development Associate - Certified 2018 CIW Advanced HTML5 & CSS3 Specialist -Certified 2018 CIW User Interface Designer - Certified 2019 LPI Linux Essentials - Certified 2020

# Skills

- Bilingual Spanish & English
- Team player
- Flexible thinker & adaptive learner
- Database entry
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Attention to detail